

907 Forest Drive, Garner, NC 27529 (919) 921-7562 massengillashley@icloud.com ashleymassengill.github.io

ashleymassengill.com

# **OVERVIEW**

Through my experiences, I have learned where my strengths lie. I enjoy writing code and turning designs into interactive products through HTML and CSS. My goal is to continue growing my experience and knowledge in ways that allow me to tap into the creative and organized sides of my personality to create a product that is the best outcome for everyone.

### **STRENGTHS**

★ Creative Thinking

★ Eye for Detail

★ Analytical Thinking

★ Extreme Efficiency

★ Teaching Skills

★ Organization

### **SKILLS**

★ Responsive Design

★ Design Theory

★ 508/ADA Compliance

★ Code Review

★ Cross Browser Testing

### **WORK HISTORY**

Front-End Developer, Coalmarch 

Apr 2016 - Dec 2018 
Raleigh, NC

- Built and styled custom designed enterprise client sites on Drupal7 platform.
- Developed proprietary features and templates for Drupal7 based Sprowt website platform.
- Lead front-end developer and product owner on Teambuilder, Coalmarch.com.
- Team organization lead including documentation, Pantheon maintenance.

#### Database Manager, RCI, Inc.

🗓 Apr 2016 - Jul 2016 💲 Raleigh, NC

- Managed internal tech support including computer hardware, software, phone systems, servers, and website.
- Guided implementation of new AMS through search, demon, contract, setup and testing phases into training and go-live.
- Created and maintained all reporting operations for each department.

### Meetings Specialist, RCI, Inc.

i Dec 2010 - Apr 2016 \$ Raleigh, NC

- Produced event based website layouts and coding.
- Managed all event registrations for 10+ attendee events to 1500+ attedee events.
- Created all meeting collateral for international events from general education to conventions and trade shows.

# **VOLUNTEER HISTORY**

Guest Services NC State Athletics

🗓 Aug 2016 - current 🜎 Raleigh, NC

Box Office & Boutique Assistant Carolina Ballet

Aug 2010 - 2016 Raleigh, NC

# **TECHNOLOGIES**

Drupal8

HTML5 advanced

CSS3 advanced

Sass advanced

AngularJS beginner

jQuery intermediate

PHP intermediate

Git intermediate

Drupal7 advanced

Pantheon advanced

beginner

Jira advanced

Atom advanced

Adobe Illustrator intermediate

Adobe Photoshop intermediate

Adobe InDesign intermediate

Adobe Acrobat advanced

InVision Intermediate

Crystal Reports intermediate

Apple iWork advanced

Microsoft Office advanced

G Suite advanced

# **EDUCATION**

UI Design, The Iron Yard

© Oct 2016 - Jan 2017 💲 Raleigh, NC

East Carolina University

🗓 Aug 2001 - May 2003 💲 Greenville, NC

**AFFILIATIONS** 

Women Who Code Raleigh/Durham

AIGA Raleigh

Triangle UXPA